## LEONI LANDUYT

- a leoni.landuyt@hotmail.com
- h +32 474 32 92 23
- Schouwbroekstraat 64, 9921 Lievegem (Belgium)

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am an animal care student who loves nature, animals, children, adventure, travelling, sports and adrenaline. I am studious and want to do everything the best way possible. When I don't have experience with something, I am willing to work hard to learn. I am social and I am open to everyone and everything.

## **EDUCATION**

Atheneum Mariakerke
Mariakerke, Ghent • 06/2016
High School Diploma

University College Ghent
Ghent • Expected in 09/2022

**Professional Bachelor**: Agro- and Biotechnology - Animal Care

## **SKILLS**

#### Job skills

- Decent in English
- Highly reliable
- Interpersonal skills
- Flexible
- Punctual

## Scout leader skills

- Activity Organization
- Parental Involvement
- Behavior Management
- Safety Awareness
- Outdoor Events
- Leadership
- Responsibility
- Active
- Social

## **WORK HISTORY**

Sea Scouts FOS - Scout Leader Ghent, Belgium • 09/2017 - Current

- Fostered positive personal connection with each troop participant and cultivated social connections and sense of solidarity.
- Encouraged participation of all scouts in camp activities including wake-up, meals, program and rest time, supervising and assisting to guide troop members in safe and enriching activity.
- Assisted in developing and implementing program ideas, planned activities for units and evaluated program quality.
- Administered basic first aid and medications per organizational guidelines, documenting incidents and communicating details to camp director.
- Introduced games and drills, which helped students to better develop skill levels.

Centro de Recuperação do Lobo Ibérico CRLI - Wolf caretaker Gradil, Portugal • Internship • 09/2020 - 10/2020

- Monitored wolves behavior.
- Mixed and administered special food formulas to individual wolves based on unique dietary needs.
- Carrying out optimal feeding and watering schedule.
- Administered medications to animals in treatment on regular, scheduled basis and documented changes in condition.
- Followed all wolf care instructions, including dietary needs and medication regimens.
- Carrying out maintenance tasks to the center such as removing overgrowth, debris and leaves from pathways, removing and repairing fences and repainting.

## Other skills

- Creative
- Technically inclined
- Sportive
- Studious

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Driver's license AM, B, A1, A2
- Boating/sailing license + marine radio license

## **HOBBIES**

- Sea scouting Sailing
- Horse riding
- Snowboarding



#### Le Beach House - Server

Ghent, Belgium • Student Job • 07/2020 - 09/2020

- Greeted new customers, discussed specials, helped them place orders, explained menu items and suggested appropriate options for food allergy concerns, taste and interest.
- Greeted and maintained relationships with regular customers.
- Operated efficiently in high-volume setting to prepare and serve drinks and food.
- Polished glassware, bussed tables and removed debris to keep customer areas fresh and clean.
- Enhanced operational efficiency by using slow periods to restock employee and customer supplies, including ice, condiments, utensils, napkins, trays and delivery bags.
- Collected credit card, cash and gift certificate payments and dispensed change for cash transactions.

#### First In Line - Bartender

Ghent, Belgium • Student Job • 06/2018 - Current

- Organized bar inventory and storage procedures to keep stock within optimal levels and meet expected customer demands.
- Took customer orders and capitalized on opportunities to sell special beverage and food options.
- Polished glassware, bussed tables and removed debris to keep customer areas fresh and clean.
- Set up glassware, liquor and other necessary supplies for special events.

## **Uitzendgastronomie - Catering Staff**

Lovendegem, Belgium • Student Job • 09/2017 - 12/2017

- Presented food and beverages on buffet tables and drink stations to meet contract specifications and level of event formality.
- Fostered enjoyable event atmosphere through friendly guest interactions
- Cleaned and sanitized work stations to meet health department regulations.
- Cleared dishes and glassware quickly following each course.
- Maintained flexible work schedule including evenings, weekends and on-call to meet event needs.
- Executed synchronized meal service simultaneously serving multiple guests with speed and efficiency.
- Served appetizers, entrees and refilled beverages for events up to 600 guests.

## Chocolato - Barista

Ghent, Belgium • Student Job • 10/2015 - 12/2016

- Prepared coffee, cleaned dining areas, opened register and carried out other opening duties.
- Maintained supply levels in counter and customer areas to meet typical demands.
- Cleaned counters, machines, utensils and seating areas daily.
- Made and served café beverages with speed, quality and consistency.
- Controlled line and crowd with quick, efficient service.
- Pleasantly interacted with customers during hectic periods to promote fun, positive environment.
- Maintained regular and consistent attendance and punctuality.

# Benny & Peggy - Catering Staff Drongen, Belgium • Student Job • 04/2013 - 02/2015

Same as "Uitzendgastronomie"